{
    "subject": "resource/John_Richardson_(drummer)",
    "predicate": "http://xmlns.com/foaf/0.1/isPrimaryTopicOf",
    "object": "http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/John_Richardson_(drummer)",
    "human_readable": "John Richardson is the primary topic of Wikipedia page 'John Richardson (drummer)'.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.987224817276001,
            "question": "What is the primary topic covered by the Wikipedia page 'John Richardson (drummer)'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9838460683822632,
            "question": "Who is the subject of the Wikipedia page 'John Richardson (drummer)'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9089667797088623,
            "question": "Does the Wikipedia page 'John Richardson (drummer)' provide details about his life and career?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8175819516181946,
            "question": "Can you find information about John Richardson's musical career on Wikipedia?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7346675992012024,
            "question": "Is John Richardson a famous musician?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6938121318817139,
            "question": "What genre of music is John Richardson associated with?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6559634804725647,
            "question": "Is John Richardson known for his work in music?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.599473774433136,
            "question": "Has John Richardson collaborated with other musicians?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5608161091804504,
            "question": "What bands or projects has John Richardson been involved in?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5454265475273132,
            "question": "What instrument does John Richardson play?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=John Richardson is the primary topic of Wikipedia page 'John Richardson (drummer)'.",
            "html": "dbpedia_773_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What bands or projects has John Richardson been involved in?",
            "html": "dbpedia_773_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Has John Richardson collaborated with other musicians?",
            "html": "dbpedia_773_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is John Richardson known for his work in music?",
            "html": "dbpedia_773_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_773_1.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'} \n\n\n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "Based on the provided context information, I can answer your query as follows:\n\n`{'output': 'no'}`\n\nThe reason for this response is that the main topic of the provided text is not \"John Richardson (drummer)\", but rather a character named Ezekiel Richardson from the Outlander book series."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'no'}\n```\n\nExplanation: The provided context information does not mention any biography or specific details about a person named \"John Richardson\" being the primary topic of a Wikipedia page. Therefore, the statement is not supported by the given documents."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"no\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 0,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Least Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {
        "mistral": {
            "reason": "Ezekiel Richardson (not John Richardson) is the primary topic of the context information provided.",
            "category": 2
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "reason": "the context information provided refers to a character named Ezekiel Richardson, not John Richardson, which suggests that the topic of the Wikipedia page is actually about the former, not the latter.",
            "category": 2
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "reason": "The provided context focuses on Ezekiel Richardson as a character in the Outlander series, not a drummer or any other profession related to music. There is no information linking him to a Wikipedia page about a drummer named John Richardson.",
            "category": 2
        }
    }
}